[
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Tina's favorite boy band?",
    "choice1": "Boyz 4 Now",
    "choice2": "Boys II Men",
    "choice3": "One Direction",
    "choice4": "New Kids on the Block",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Bob's eccentric landlord?",
    "choice1": "Mr. Fischoeder",
    "choice2": "Mr. Frond",
    "choice3": "Hugo",
    "choice4": "Calvin Fischoeder",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the title of Tina's erotic friend fiction story?",
    "choice1": "The Hormone-iums",
    "choice2": "Two for Tina",
    "choice3": "Fifty Shades of Tina",
    "choice4": "Tina in Wonderland",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Linda's sister's name?",
    "choice1": "Gayle",
    "choice2": "Gretchen",
    "choice3": "Gloria",
    "choice4": "Giselle",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the school that the Belcher kids attend?",
    "choice1": "Wagstaff School",
    "choice2": "Springfield Elementary",
    "choice3": "Hillwood School",
    "choice4": "Greendale Academy",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Teddy's ex-wife?",
    "choice1": "Denise",
    "choice2": "Dolores",
    "choice3": "Debbie",
    "choice4": "Diana",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the mysterious graffiti artist in Bob's Burgers?",
    "choice1": "Turd Burglar",
    "choice2": "Spray Master",
    "choice3": "The Chalk Bandit",
    "choice4": "Graffiti Ghost",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the magazine that Tina writes for in one episode?",
    "choice1": "Teen Vogue",
    "choice2": "The Mad Pooper",
    "choice3": "Horse & Hound",
    "choice4": "The Thundergirls Gazette",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Bob's favorite holiday?",
    "choice1": "Thanksgiving",
    "choice2": "Christmas",
    "choice3": "Halloween",
    "choice4": "Burgerfest",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the boat that Bob buys?",
    "choice1": "The Sea Shanty",
    "choice2": "The Love Boat",
    "choice3": "The Indecision",
    "choice4": "The Queen of Hearts",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Linda's favorite alcoholic drink that she often mentions and enjoys?",
    "choice1": "Wine",
    "choice2": "Vodka",
    "choice3": "Whiskey",
    "choice4": "Tequila",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Bob's Burgers Christmas episode 'Bob Rest Ye Merry Gentle-Mannequins,' what festive display does Bob create in the restaurant window?",
    "choice1": "A Santa Claus mannequin",
    "choice2": "A Nativity scene",
    "choice3": "A winter wonderland diorama",
    "choice4": "A gingerbread house",
    "answer": 3
  }
]
